{"data":[{"question":"I would like to do ___ I can do for you.","a":"what little service","b":"what few service","c":"which little service","d":"which few service","answer":"1","explain":"\n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Who ___ has common sense can believe such a superstition?","a":"who","b":"which","c":"but","d":"that","answer":"4","explain":"\n- That: can be used for people and things and as subject and object in defining relative clauses","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"My father has made me ___ I am.","a":"who","b":"which","c":"what","d":"that","answer":"3","explain":"\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- That normally refers to things but it may refer to a class or type of person. \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n+ What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n+We prefer which when the number of choices is limited ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"That is the town ___ he was born.","a":"which","b":"where","c":"when","d":"why","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Where refers to place \n- When refers to time \n- Why refers to reason \n- Which refers to thing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"She does not see the reason ___ he would like to join them.","a":"why","b":"when","c":"how","d":"where","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Where refers to place \n- When refers to time \n- Why refers to reason \n- How refers to means\/method or way to do something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The day will soon come ___ man will set foot on another planet.","a":"which","b":"when","c":"why","d":"where","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Where refers to place \n- When refers to time \n- Why refers to reason \n- Which refers to thing ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"We traveled together as far as Chicago,___ we parted.","a":"when","b":"which","c":"why","d":"where","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Where refers to place \n- When refers to time \n- Why refers to reason \n- Which refers to thing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"I was about to leave,___ she came in.","a":"where","b":"which","c":"when","d":"how","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Where refers to place \n- When refers to time \n- Why refers to reason \n- How refers to means\/method or way to do something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"___ the children sleep.","a":"That's where","b":"There's","c":"There's in which","d":"That's","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Where refers to place \n- Which refers to thing \n- \"That's and there's\" is not suitable in terms of meaning ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"I will invite ___ my daughter loves.","a":"whoever","b":"whomever","c":"whichever","d":"whatever","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Whomever: used to say that it does not matter whom (the object) does something, is in a particular place \n- Whoever: used to say that it does not matter whom (the Subject) does something, is in a particular place \n- Whichever: used to say that it does not matter which thing or person is chosen because the result will be the same \n- Whatever: any or all of the things that are wanted, needed, or possible","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"62","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}